csschopper.com 2018-01-02

# CSSChopper's Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy (“Privacy Statement”) owned by CSSChopper reflects its commitment and transparency towards the privacy sustained for its customers and visitors, who interact with CSSChopper.com anyhow. Our privacy section highlights that we might use the IP address of our site visitors in order to administer and assist them in analyzing the problems using our web servers. For this reason, we require the personal and/ or contact information about the site users in order to provide effective information to them about the company. 

Note: CSSChopper.com may have shared the links and content of the varied other websites here, for which CSSChopper is not lawfully accountable for any such content as well privacy practice, applicable to their websites. 

### Gathering your personal Information voluntarily 

From the means you connect with us such as through order form, request form etc., we collect your personal information to identify you using your first name, last name, contact address, email address, Date of Birth, gender, phone number etc. Such type of information is voluntarily submitted by the user that helps them to communicate better the company. 

However, CSSChopper pays stringent attention on how your sensitive information is used and shared. Additionally, we assure that your confidential information is perfectly safeguard with us and it will not be sold, disclosed, updated or shared with anybody in any case other than our reliable resources & partners that provide assistance and support to your project. 

### Information collected through technology

Generally when you visit our website, our web servers gather the information about your IP address/ domain names in order to analyze the statistics such as number of visits made on the website, pages viewed, time spent on the site by the user etc. The purpose of evaluating the statistics is to take measurable steps in boosting the website services to enhance the customer’s experience and serving them far better than before. We collect information using cookies and navigational data (such as URL) to find the date & time of the visit, browser type, operating system etc. 

### Use of gathered information

The gathered information that is, submitted by you or collected by us is helpful in making our services better for enhanced and personalized customer experience like quickly responding to the request against the queries, facilitating the quote, process transactions and so on. The gathered information will be shared with the third party in cases, if:

  * We feel that it is necessary in order to fulfill your ordered services
  * Providing better consultation as per your service request

However, we may also use your personal information in providing promotional emails, RSS feed, electronic newsletters and latest offers related to your business’ interests but only after your consent to “SUBSCRIBE” and at anytime it can be unsubscribe as per the request. 

### Your Rights

You have complete rights to stop receiving marketing emails, newsletter, RSS Feed and other sort of electronic communication through “unsubscribe” feature selected as per your rights. 

### Privacy statement updates

Each time you use CSSChopper, you agree with the entire practices and policies demonstrated in the privacy statements. All the rights are reserved with CSSChopper, therefore the information offered for the privacy practices can be amended, altered and/ or updated without the prior notice at any point of time. We recommend you to review the privacy statements time-to-time to clearly understand our process for privacy. Subsequent use of our site and its services shall indicate that you are acquainted with the amendment made to the policies and agree the terms and conditions cordially. 

### Information Security 

CSSChopper sustains the high security benchmarks to safeguard your personal information from getting missed or misused, so to assure that your personal information is free from every risk. 

### Contact us

The information provided by you is incomplete, incorrect or updated, then please send us an email to get it updated soon with us. Also, if you find any query regarding our privacy statement, feel free to contact us: 

Sparx IT Solutions Pvt. Ltd. A-2, sector 63, Noida, UP (India)   
Phone: +91­ 120 4735100   
Email: [sales@csschopper.com](mailto:sales@csschopper.com)

**SUBSCRIBE for discounts & news **

Rated 4.9 out of 5.0 for CSSChopper service by 9961 clients on over 15000\+ projects.

### From the blog

[PSD to HTML / HTML5 Conversion with Popular Frameworks and CSS Types](http://www.csschopper.com/blog/psd-to-html-html5-conversion-popular-frameworks-css-types/ "PSD to HTML / HTML5 Conversion with Popular Frameworks and CSS Types")

Due to rapid web development & advancement in current market scenario, businesses are demanding the most appealing websites. Thus, they opt for the best PSD to from a... [ read more](http://www.csschopper.com/blog/psd-to-html-html5-conversion-popular-frameworks-css-types/)

CSSChopper, a leading player of India in web development industry, offers flat 50% discount on all HTML projects. We care our clients a lot, so we bring this special for... [ read more](http://www.csschopper.com/blog/last-day-offer-50-off-html-projects/)

### CLIENT ASKED QUESTIONS

#### How good are you in mobile application development?

#### Are all the stats on your website true?

#### Is it possible to meet your representative in the USA?

INDUSTRY NEWS: The WordPress.com’s parent company, Automattic has recently bought popular wooCommerce plugin for converting WordPress to e-store easily. http://goo.gl/TNBKPd

## More reasons to start with us

### Birthday Special for Existing Clients

Order on your birthday and get 10% off with a coupon code as a gift from us. 

_3_

### Credit Points - even a single penny matters 

We offer you credit points for each and every penny that you spend on our website for the project. You can encash these points on your next order. 

_4_

### Special Discount to Clients

We love our returning customer as it instills confidence in us. To acknowledge our clients’ trust on us for, we offer them a flat 15% discount on the total cost of the 2nd project. 

_1_

### Refer & Earn

We reward our clients who refer us to others by offering them a bonus discount of 10% on the total project cost. Sit back in a cafe or at home and earn bonus discounts. Know more 

_2_

### Birthday Special for Existing Clients

Order on your birthday and get 10% off with a coupon code as a gift from us. 

_3_

### Credit Points - even a single penny matters 

We offer you credit points for each and every penny that you spend on our website for the project. You can encash these points on your next order. 

_4_

### Special Discount to Clients

We love our returning customer as it instills confidence in us. To acknowledge our clients’ trust on us for, we offer them a flat 15% discount on the total cost of the 2nd project. 

_1_

### Refer & Earn

We reward our clients who refer us to others by offering them a bonus discount of 10% on the total project cost. Sit back in a cafe or at home and earn bonus discounts. Know more 

_2_

### Birthday Special for Existing Clients

Order on your birthday and get 10% off with a coupon code as a gift from us. 

_3_

### Credit Points - even a single penny matters 

We offer you credit points for each and every penny that you spend on our website for the project. You can encash these points on your next order. 

_4_

  *   * 

### Client Area (MyChopps)

Now manage invoices, project payments, project & scope ordering/revision, raise helpdesk tickets & do much more with MyChopps. 

_3_

### Project Management System (PMS)

Customized PMS to let the clients easily track the status of the project and contact the project team as and when required. 

_4_

### Cost for initiating a project

Start with an upfront payment of 10% of the project cost. 

_1_

### Free Technical Support

We offer 30 days of free support and assistance after the project delivery for all custom and CMS projects. 

_2_

### Client Area (MyChopps)

Now manage invoices, project payments, project & scope ordering/revision, raise helpdesk tickets & do much more with MyChopps. 

_3_

### Project Management System (PMS)

Customized PMS to let the clients easily track the status of the project and contact the project team as and when required. 

_4_

### Cost for initiating a project

Start with an upfront payment of 10% of the project cost. 

_1_

### Free Technical Support

We offer 30 days of free support and assistance after the project delivery for all custom and CMS projects. 

_2_

### Client Area (MyChopps)

Now manage invoices, project payments, project & scope ordering/revision, raise helpdesk tickets & do much more with MyChopps. 

_3_

### Project Management System (PMS)

Customized PMS to let the clients easily track the status of the project and contact the project team as and when required. 

_4_

  *   * 

### SATISFACTION GUARANTEE

CSSChopper strongly ensure for a high level of satisfaction among our potential clients.

### NON DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT

CSSChopper proclaims 100% NDA Guarantee to protect client’s "Confidential Data" 

### MONEY BACK GUARANTEE

CSSChopper refunds received amount under conditions mentioned in *Money Back Guarantee Policy.
